I'm gonna turn this off for a minute.
Thank you.
Oh, this one. Oh, okay.
Hello. - Hello.
I wonder if she's watching.
Shall we say hello? We're Hinatazaka46.
Nice to meet you.
Say your name. Sure.
I'm Kumi Sasaki. Mana Takase. Selina Milk.
Hiyori Amagishi, Haruka Yamashita, Hinano Kamimura.
These six will be delivering the live broadcast today.
Thank you very much.
The reason why we're here today is...
We are going to start our Happy Train Tour on August 30th!
Yes, that's right, a train!
So we're going to take the tour a little bit further.
Even more!
We hope you will enjoy the tour even more!
We were rehearsing like this until five minutes ago.
Just now? Just now. We just finished.
Why don't you look at it?
If you look carefully, you'll see evidence of our hard work.
Like a little sweat.
There's a reason why the members are here.
I LOVE the members who came today.
The members who came today will be traveling around the country.
I'd like to say they are local members.
I'd like to ask them to introduce some of the local delicacies
I'd like to introduce you to some local delicacies.
No, no, no, no, no.
Yes!
How scary!
There's a senior in front of me.
Yeah, I noticed.
Do you want to check this one?
It's the order of rotation.It's the order of rotation, so there's nothing to be done.
Well then, let's get on with it.
There's a lot of food lined up there.
They look so good!
I can't wait to try them!
I'll be there from August 30th.
From Osaka.
From Osaka!
Ta-da!
This way please!
I'm from Osaka.
I'm from Osaka, so I'm happy to be able to go around from Osaka.
I'm so happy.
The first one is Uffu Pudding!
I was thinking of octopus balls or okonomiyaki.
Or okonomiyaki.
I don't know...
I think everyone would go for that.
I dare you to choose this one.
Ouf pudding
It means "egg" in French.
Is that so?
Just like the name.
Bonjour!
Bonjour.
Yeah.
It's egg rich.
I've been around a lot.
At school and among mothers
They say the pudding here is really good.
That's right.
It's always talked about.
The mothers say it's delicious.
So I went to buy some.
It's so good!
That's why I want you all to try it.That's why I want you all to try it.
I'd like you all to try it.
It's like people in the know.
But lately
He wants to eat it.
He's eating it.
After this.
And the second one is Santarashi Komochi
But still...
Actually, it's a gift.
I bought it for everyone quite a while ago.
I've thought about it before
I've thought about it.
Have you?
It was a big hit.
I liked it a lot.
When I go back to my hometown in Osaka and come back to Tokyo.
I bought one for everyone.
I buy one for myself.
I even buy some for myself.
for myself when I go back to Tokyo.
Among all the souvenirs from Osaka
I love it so much
my favorite
I love it so much.
I just heard from the manager
You can be a little louder.
I don't mean "tauten it up.
Tighten it up.
Stretch it out.
He's on to us.
She noticed you.
You've been pretty vocal.
But...
I don't think you guys heard me.
So, everyone.Hey, guys.
It's not an "ugh.
It's not an "uh-huh." It's not an "uh-huh.
It's an egg.
Egg pudding.
Do you have egg pudding? I have it ready.
Okay, bye.
There's a lot of stuff here.
This one, too.
Can I take a snack?
Pudding.
Oh, my God.
Let's eat it.
You can eat it.
Here you go.
Congratulations.
I'm watching Mento.
I'm watching you.
Here you go.
They all taste the same.
We've got the right number of people.
We don't have to play games or anything.
That's so sweet of you. You're all so sweet.
That's so sweet. Thank you.
I'll start with the pudding.
Bon appétit.
How do I get this?
Oh, soooo...
It's gonna fall off.
Oh, I don't know. Market.
Spoiler alert.
It's a little bit of a spoiler.
I'll just leave it right here.
Thank you.
Sorry about that.I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I was just in a flap.
It was just a flurry.
It was like it just started.
That sounded good.
I like it.
This time...
I used to love it.
I've been preparing a flane.
I don't know...
Put it in front.
Thank you.
I'm sorry.
You can eat in front of the manahi.
Is that okay?
I want to hear what the manajeis have to say about it.
Looks delicious.
It's got a little bit of milk on top.
Oh, my God.
Milk? Is it okay?
Yeah, eat it.
Help yourself.
I'll have some while you get ready.
Yes, ma'am.
Bon appétit.
I'll tell you what I think of it and we'll get started.
I think we're all ready to eat.
Then we'll eat.
Bon appétit!
Looks delicious.
Oh, wow!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Eeeee!
Okoloffee!
Ohhhhh, here it is!
I don't think I've ever seen okoloffee with such an oction!
Super tasty!
Let's eat it!
Let's have some!
Bon appétit!
It's really insanely delicious!
So sweet.
But it's so sweet that it really is a mess after a meal or something.
I want you all to try it.
This is amazing!
Oh, my God, it's so poofy.
Is it oofy?
It's so oofy.
Mmm-hmm.
Delicious.
Plain is my favorite.
But now it's like tiramisu.
Like tiramisu like tiramisu flavor.
I heard they have a lot of flavors.
So please try them too!
If plain is not enough for you...
I recommend it!
Delicious!
It's so delicious!
It doesn't have caramel.
There are some with caramel...
It's not too sweet, but it's delicious!
I like the plain ones the best.
Okay, everyone.
Please try it.
I made it myself.
I didn't make it myself.
It's delicious.
They say it's delicious.They say it's delicious.
I'll have three of these.
I'll have three pieces.
Mr. Midorati, I think we should take them one by one.
Here you go.
Thank you.
You should put one of the puddings on the table, too.
You can put the pudding here if you want.
Are you still eating?
Can I?
Later. Let's eat.
Wipe your hands once.
I'll use a toothpick.
I found toothpicks.
A toothpick.
Here you go.
I'm counting on you.
toothpick
Thank you very much.
Then, from the back, please.
Eat.
Bon appétit.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Is this some kind of pudding party?
Oh, yeah.
That's what this is about.
That's why we're asking everyone to eat.
Eat.
You can eat, Hinano.
Bon appétit.
Looks delicious.
Thank you so much.Thank you.
The end. Thank you for watching.
Eat up! Eat!
Eat freely!
Really.
Is there any for me?
Yum!
There's plenty!
I want some!
You can have some when you go to Osaka.
You can get these at the airport.
You can find them at the airport or at souvenir stores.
I'll have some too.
Bon appétit!
I ate it.
Here you go.
So cute!
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
Mochimaruko
Really delicious!
It's so good!
I'm so happy.
I'm happy.
Let's eat.
Delicious!
Mochi Mochi
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Yummy!
Yum na fee
Yummy feast!
Yummy!
Yummy.
What book?
Kizuta. Is it good?Kizuta delicious?
Delicious.
A little.
A little bit.
Are you okay? Pair.
Water.
Do you have any water?
You've prepared so much for us.
Only water is missing.
It's delicious.
Yes, it is.
It's water-based.
Santara-shi thick.
Santara City thick.
Delicious.
This was Manafie's gourmet introduction to Osaka.
Please come to Osaka, everyone.
Please come to Osaka.
I'll go on to the next question.
May I go on?
I'm just going to make light of it.
I was just saying that I was a little bit watery.
You said it's a bit watery.
Let me introduce myself.
I am from Yokohama, Kanagawa Prefecture.
I thought you were from Indonesia.
I thought it was Indonesia.
I thought it was Indonesian gourmet.
I hope to go to Indonesia someday.
I want to do my best so that we can all have lunch at Hinatazaka.
I want to do my best.
Let's go to England, too.
I want to go to England.
I'm from there.I mean, I'm from there.
I was just spending time there.
I was born in Kanagawa.
I was born in Yokohama.
This time you are going to perform at Yokohama Arena, right?
The tour is at Yokohama Arena.
I'm going to perform live.
I'm from Kanagawa.
What is it?
I would like to introduce recommended gourmet food.
Jan.
Here they are.
Hamanashi and Haman grapes.
Oh.
This is.
It says pear and grape.
These are fruits grown in Yokohama.
Fruits grown in Yokohama.
Yes.
Yokohama Hama looks strong.
You see?
It's a Chinese character.
I wrote something on it.
I wrote something in a supermarket.
It's not easy to buy at supermarkets.
There is a direct sales shop.
Yokohama City is full of them.
You can buy them there.
Freshly picked.
Because they are freshly harvested, they are fresher and taste so much better.
Pears and grapes.
I want to eat them.
Then, please bring me some more.
Hamanashi pears.
They're beautiful.
I don't know anyone in Kawasaki.He doesn't know anyone in Kawasaki.
Oh, I see. Yokohama.
It's in this direction.
Hamagishi.
It's big.
Thanks for the quiz.
Hamanashi and Hamagishi.
Hamanashi, Hamabudou, Hamagishi.
Hamagishi.
How do you eat them?
Pears are in the back.
Pears are pear tanto.
This is Hamabudou.
Chiba is famous for pears, too.
Well, everyone, please eat it.
What do you think?
Not all fruits grown in Yokohama can be called "Hama-nashi" or "Hama-budou",
Only those that have undergone a certain kind of examination and have been certified can call themselves Hama-nashi (pears) and Hama-budou (grapes).
How do you like it?
They are totally, totally delicious.
Yes, they are.
Oh, Kui-chan, you're eating grapes.
They are delicious.
He's eating them beautifully.
But they're not as big as yours.
Really?
They're big.
And these beach grapes...
Well, let's see.
They're big.
Bigger than our faces, bigger than everyone else's faces.
That's amazing.
We have small faces.
Yeah.
Yes, yes, it's that good,Yes, it's that good,
Delicious.
If you happen to be in the neighborhood and see a place that sells them, please stop by.
I'm sorry, but I changed my seat,
Daiki, Haruharu, yes, where are you from?
I'm from Aichi Prefecture.
Oh, wow!
Your first time in Aichi Prefecture.
There are many things in Aichi Prefecture,
I like shiruko sandwiches and...,
What was it again?
Alphabet chocolate.
Wow!
You know shiruko sandwiches, right?
Yes, I do.
Do you have it?
We have shiruko sandwiches here,
Oh, there it is!
Let's eat it.
Thanks!
Here it is.
This is famous, isn't it?
This is from Hokkaido,
Azukio's,
Azuki O's,
Oh, he wrote it himself.
It's a hard type,
Yes.
It's a cookie.
Can I eat this?
Yes.
I eat them often.
I like Shiruko.
When I'm hungry, I just grab one.
It's delicious.Delicious.
And the second one is alphabet chocolate,
Have you seen these?
Yes, I have.
Was this in Aichi?
Actually, it is from Aichi.
It is a food of Aichi,
It's chocolate, but it's made in Aichi,
It is a little bit rich.
I see.
I ate it when I was a child.
I ate it.
Please put them together in getteling or something.
This is also the first time I've heard of this being called alphabet chocolate.
So it has a name.
Well, let's all do it together and see what alphabet we can come up with.
What are you after?
Bon appétit.
One.
Okay.
Okay, I'll go with Parina's eclair.
I don't know.
Okay, I'm on it.
Cut.
I got that one, too.
Okay, then. Z.
It's cool.
Z.
You sure? It's cool.
I want a Z.
S.
C.
I'll take an A.
Yay.
What was that?
T.T
I am U
U
I'm impressed
There are ways to enjoy
even before you eat it.
I will eat
very rich
thank you
Summer Puff
You went to Aichi, right?
Other than that, it was peorin
Sweets.
Piolin Challenge
Mr. Piolin is
Oni Manjuu
Good morning manjuu
Onimanju
It was an ogre's world
I'm going to think of people in the devil's world.
You mean?
It's from something.
There's a sweet potato in it.
It's a kind of Japanese confectionery.
I used to make it by hand and eat it with everyone when I was little.
I see.
The name has a strong impact.
It's like "Onimanju.
It looks strong.
It's sweet.
I want some!
I want some.
I want some... Onimanju.
So then...
Haruharu isHaru Haru wa
Shiruko Sandwich and Alphabet Chocolate
Delicious!
Please try them. Maybe as a souvenir.
Aichi Aichi Minasan Let's have fun!
Let's have fun!
I wonder if everyone's here by now.
But I guess a lot of them are coming back.
I'm sorry.
I've been slammed.
It's a mess.
Yes, please.
Okay, then.
Hi, I'm Hiyotan.
My food recommendation is...
Fukuoka has a lot to offer.
There are a lot of things I recommend.
Among them, I'd like to recommend
I've prepared the core ones.
I've prepared
Petit milk baguettes and
These cookies
Maple Tree Drops
country cookies.
I've prepared them.
I love it all!
Looks delicious.
This is the petit milk baguette.
Looks so good!
Yum yum!
Thank you so much.
Looks so good!
Looks delicious!
Yum yum yum!Yum!!!
This is my mom's favorite.
Yes, she did.
I used to eat them when I was little when my mom and I would have tea together.
So stylish!
Very stylish.
You have tea with your mom?
I used to have tea with my mom.
The end.
We're done.
Can I eat?
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
I'm introducing Fukuoka now.
I'm Fukuoka girl.
I'm a Fukuoka girl.
Is this sold by the bakery?
No, it is. Look.
Oh, it's a bakery.
Oh, there's no bakery.
Bon appétit.
Oh, my gosh.
It's milk.
Yes, it is.
Bakery.
Thank you very much.
Welcome home.
It's good.
It's warm.
Yes, it is.
It's really good. It's a little bit chewy.
It's French bread, so it's a little hard, but it's good.
It's delicious.
Sweet and salty.Sweet and salty.
It's sweet and salty and soooo good.
Delicious.
Yes, it continues, there is a lot.
Yes, it is.
Thank you very much.
These are cookies from a place called Bang Forest that I used to bring to ballet recitals.
I especially like this one called Maple Tree Drops.
There are different kinds of cookies.
This kind of cookie.
These ice cream balls, what are they called?
Snowballs.
Like snowballs.
Can I eat this one?
Yes, I like it.
I like it.
Handly cookies.
You sure you don't mind?
I'll have some too.
Let's eat.
Please eat.
Okay.
Bon appétit.
Cookie.
Yes, so, I'll have it.
It's like a candy party.
It's making me hungry, everyone.
Yes, we are.
We're running out of time for a candy party.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Oh, I'm sorry.
We're on a bit of a time limit.
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
I'm in Fukuoka.I'm in Fukuoka.
Hiyotan recommended it to me.
Is it good?
I'm glad.
I'll have some of those delicious country cookies.
Okay.
Eat up, Haruharu.
Thank you very much.
They melt in an instant.
They melt in your mouth.
Melt in your mouth.
Float.
Just a little bit
Because it's a drop
It's so good
I love it
Delicious
Nostalgic taste
I like it. It's a nostalgic taste.
Yum! Yum!
Oh, my God.
It's really good.
It's really good. It's really good. It's so buttery.
It's so buttery, I don't know... and when I said "nose," it almost made a big ball of butter.
Butter, butter, butter!
It's that rich and delicious.
It's a very nostalgic taste. It's the same old, same old deliciousness.
It's so good, you should try it!
Fukuoka has a lot of gourmet food, but I don't think people know about this.
I don't think people know about it.
Bank forest. It's good. It's surrounded by coconut.
Yes, there are many kinds. It's delicious.
It's delicious.
Okay, and then we'll go to Miyagi.
We don't have any members from Miyagi.There are no members from Miyagi, so it's us.
Hinanosan is here.
Miyagi-chan did some research for me.
She looked up some gourmet foods I've been wanting to try.
Oh, I saw it.
These are o-hagi from Sendai Shufu no Ten, Shufu no Ten Nishiichi.
Ohagi!
There seem to be various kinds of o-hagi.
Rumor has it that they sell over 25,000 of them a day!
Wow, they look super delicious!
Ohagi, ohagi!
They have sweet bean paste, sesame and soybean flour!
Wow!
Which one is it?
By the way...
I've got something for you today.
What?
What? It stopped?
Stopped?
It's gone.
Aah!
I'm afraid it's a little...
I want some!
I couldn't prepare it,
I thought I would like to try it at Sendai Park when I visit Megane Sendai.
Aaah!
I'll look forward to that!
Let's look forward to it!
Let's eat at the same time as our customers.Let's eat at the same time as our customers.
Yes, we should eat at the same time as our customers.
Let's eat at the same time as our customers.
Sir!
Good morning.
Let's eat!
Yes, so it was a bit of a slap in the face,
Yes, sir.
Back?
Let's go back.
Thank you.
So, uh, what year is it?
Six years?
Yeah. - No?
No, five years?
Five?
I'll be here for 5 years,
I'm looking forward to it.
Of course I'm looking forward to the live concerts,
but also the food and the gourmet food,
We are looking forward to it,
We are looking forward to the live concert, of course, but we are also looking forward to the food and the gourmet food,
We are looking forward to the live concert, of course, but we are also looking forward to the food and the gourmet food.
There are so many other things to do in the sun,
If you have any recommendations, please let us know,
If you have any other recommendations, please let me know.
Please let me know.
When you say "katoshi," do you mean "katoshi" or "katoshi"?
Katooshi.
Gatoshi. Gatoshi.It's "GOTOSHI". GOTOSHI.
You like it.
Yes, I do.
I'm sorry, I'm a little busy,
But, you know..,
Live performance today?
Of course you are looking forward to the concert, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
And, you know, that song.
That song?
That song.
Yes, that song.
That song,
Well, I didn't say that we are going to play it on the tour,
I didn't say that.
I haven't said it, but I thought I'd practice it just in case,
I really want to make it up with everyone in the sun,
This is a song that I really want to make up with everyone in the audience,
I'd like to make this song together with the people of the sun, so... Yes.
I'm going to practice this song,
From now on,
Can I join you all in practicing it?
Yes!
Thank you!
Let's do it!
Hey, sunshine!
Music!
H! I! N!
A B A 4 T G A I N A T A 4 T G I'll be with you the rest of my life.
Hey, Sunshine, where are you watching from?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, Sunshine. I'm the only one you see.
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Shoo shoo shoo shoo
Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey Hey
Tutururururururur.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, heyHey Sunshine, the neighbors are with us
La la la la la
Yay, yay, yay, yay
One, two, three.
Hey!
Can I do this freely?
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Nothing to be ashamed of.
Hey!
You can say "whoo
And say it when you want to say it.
Say it when you want to say it
It's complicated
Hey, hey, hey, sun
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
all the way, all the way
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
H I M A T A 46
The best in the world
Masyu
Just a little bit of this first number.
I'll be riding fullback.
You can say "whoo" if you want.
No, it's not.
I'm just a little excited.
But it's really nothing to be ashamed of.
We're going to make it up as we go along.
I want everyone to enjoy the show.
I'd be very happy if you could remember that call.
Please do.
I didn't say I would sing.
No, I didn't.
I'm practicing.
Just in case.Just in case.
Just in case. I'm practicing for someday.
That's right.
And I haven't told you guys much about this.
I made up a call-out for this tour.
I see.
That's right.
Last time it was Happy Smile Tour.
Happy Chachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachachacha
Smile.
I was doing the "happy smile" thing.
Yes, we did.
We were doing it together, right?
We made a little happy train this year, too.
Here.
Thank you.
You put in a good show.
Can I do it here?
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
I'll be aggressive.
I'll do it.
Happy train.
Rumble, rattle, rattle!
Let's go!
Hee hee hee
It's called "Hee-hee"!
So cute!
I'd love to see you guys in the sun.
I think you can have a penlight.
while saying "rattling rattling rattling".
I want you to do the rattling rattling rattling rattling rattling rattling rattling rattling rattling
I want you to do the last hiccup, too.
Hiccup.
Like a hoo-hoo.Like a ho-ho-ho.
Like at the time of departure.
I wanted to do something like that with everyone.
I could have done it right off the bat on the tour.
But I don't know what kind of atmosphere we'll have.
I want you to do it with me.
So I thought I'd teach you while we're still here.
Can I do this last one?
Yes, please.
Okay, here we go.
Happy train.
Clang, clang, clang.
Let's go!
Hee hee
Yay!
Thank you
Thank you very much
I'm so happy.
That's great.
Everyone's doing it.
You're so sweet.
I don't know if I'll do it.
Please do it.
I thought it would make the tour more fun if we had this shout-out or something like that.
So please join us and shout it out!
I've learned how to shout now.
I'd like to ask you to speak up!
Enjoy the tour!
Enjoy the tour and eat lots of delicious food!
I hope you will enjoy the Happy Train Tour
I hope you enjoy the tour with Hinatazaka.
Yes, ma'am.
Now that that's all said and done...
Is there anything left to say?Do you guys have any last words?
Hmmm...
It's okay.
It's still hot, folks.
Really.
But it's like the sun.
Sometimes it's even hotter than the sun.
Take care, Mr. Chairman, and please get some of the cute goods we've brought out for you,
I'm going to enjoy the Happy Train Tour with you all.
Yes, that's it for today. I'm sorry for the mess.
Yes, really. But I got it out. It was fun to eat a lot of delicious food.
Yes, thank you very much for today.
See you again.
Bye bye.
I'll turn it off.